<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Julie's Document Website on My New Hugo Site</title><link>https://example.org/</link><description>Recent content in Julie's Document Website on My New Hugo Site</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>28-01-2025</title><link>https://example.org/delphi/devjournal/28-01-2025/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.org/delphi/devjournal/28-01-2025/</guid><description>Intro It's been weeks, maybe even months since I've touched this project... oh god. I started finally implementing the renderer I created in the delphirender module. Starting with a very simple Flow layout that just places elements after each other. I'll implement the rest of the layout once I know the configuration and projection of entities is correct. Afterword It's 7 hours later. I hate this project... I spent almost all of today thinking about and fixing issues related to the most simple parts of rendering and layout possible.</description></item><item><title>January 2025 Event - Ravager Escape</title><link>https://example.org/arcadius/events/jan-2025/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.org/arcadius/events/jan-2025/</guid><description>General Concept The general concept of the event is to escape from many Ravagers chasing the player. The player is spawned at the edge of a hill, atop which lies several targets the player must break with snow balls. The player acquires these snow balls by wondering around the hill and dodging Ravagers. Once enough snowballs have been gotten, the player is able to break all targets at the top of the hill and the event ends.</description></item><item><title>05-02-2025</title><link>https://example.org/delphi/devjournal/05-02-2025/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.org/delphi/devjournal/05-02-2025/</guid><description>Today I'll most likely be fixing yesterday's bugs, getting the Flow layout completely functional with auto margins and stuff. I started by adding support the box-sizing property to Chimera and NLayout. The offset bug I described yesterday. The blue is where the black background is intended to be located. The item element (pickaxe) is also wildly offset from where it is intended to be. Another bug to fix... On top of the previous bug, when a page is spawned, the backgrounds, outlines and anything other than content is blank, resulting in this.</description></item><item><title>NLayout Engine</title><link>https://example.org/delphi/layout/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.org/delphi/layout/</guid><description>Introduction This document describes the process of writing the NLayout engine that executes layout for Delphi and how it works. This part, the layout engine, has been the most difficult part of the Delphi project to date, executing layout with so many variables that interact in so many different ways depending on layout context and such. The layout engine is part of the delphirender module which handles DOM rendering and Minecraft entity management.</description></item><item><title>Event Setup rules and guides</title><link>https://example.org/arcadius/events/rules/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.org/arcadius/events/rules/</guid><description>Event Rules The following checks must be passed during testing for an event to be considered in 'acceptable' conditions: Dying in the event must remove you from the event instantly and nullify any potential score gain, as well as remove any event-provided items and/or effects. Quitting in the event must do the same as above. It should be impossible to enter the event with potion effects, they must be either: Cleared upon entering Prevented from entering if they possess potion effects Entering the event should function perfectly each time Exiting the event should function perfectly each time Completing the event, different from exiting, should follow the event's context and assign scores only if: The player&amp;#39;s score is higher than their record The event uses the assign-only-if-score-greater rule Alt accounts are not permitted to gain score on the same ground as main accounts, when dealing with an alt, one of the following methods must be used The alt is unable to enter (preferred) The alt is unable to gain score The alt&amp;#39;s score is given to the main The follwing are optional checks which apply on a per-event basis:</description></item><item><title>Arcadian Religion</title><link>https://example.org/arcadius/religion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.org/arcadius/religion/</guid><description>Abstract Religion in the world of Arcadius is polytheistic, worship is split between several gods, and you pray to the god that's relevant to what you're struggling with. For example, if you need luck on a journey over sea, you'd pray to the sea god or goddess. Gods Note: The names used in this list are meant to be faction independent. Faction specific names are listed below. Main Gods Imperator Divius The First Emperor, ascended to godhood after death, the hero-god of humanity.</description></item><item><title>Design Document</title><link>https://example.org/arcadius/dungeons/design/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.org/arcadius/dungeons/design/</guid><description>Abstract The Dungeons, generally, is a rougelike feature of ArcadiusMC, similar to games like Hades, and Pressure (Roblox), with ULTRAKILL serving as inspiration as well. Players will enter the randomly-generated dungeons, fight through rooms of enemies until they find a boss room, fight the boss and then advance on to the next level. The purpose of this document is to outline the methods of implementation for the dungeons. Dungeon Structure The structures that will comprise the Dungeons' levels will be made with the "</description></item><item><title>Dungeons Design Document</title><link>https://example.org/arcadius/dungeons/designdoc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.org/arcadius/dungeons/designdoc/</guid><description>Introduction This document will outline the way players interact with the Dungeons and how systems of the dungeons work. Setup This section describes the way the players enter and prepare for the dungeons. Players can enter the Dungeons at a Dungeon Lobby area, where they are given an option to join an existing dungeon party or create their own. Joining Parties can be joined in one of 2 ways: Be invited, or request to join.</description></item><item><title>Merchants</title><link>https://example.org/arcadius/merchants/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.org/arcadius/merchants/</guid><description>Introduction This document describes a system of merchants and tradesmen that richer players can interact with. This sytem allows players to give large quantities of items to merchants, who then "embark" on a voyage to sell the goods overseas. All funds earned from selling are then returned to the player(s) from whom the items came. Purpose The purpose of the merchants is to provide a way for late-game, richer players to spend their money and earn more without using farms and mass-selling.</description></item><item><title>The First Emperor</title><link>https://example.org/arcadius/first-emperor/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.org/arcadius/first-emperor/</guid><description>Abstract The First Emperor is an almost mythical figure that is worshipped as a god. The true identity of him has since been long forgotten, with each faction that vies over the Empire claiming their faction to be descended from the First Emperor. The real story of the emperor is unknown, even his name is contested. It is unknown if he had children or any descendants. Variations This section will summarize the variations of the Emperor's story that each faction considers true, and then will summarize the real story.</description></item><item><title>The Latins Senate</title><link>https://example.org/arcadius/senate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.org/arcadius/senate/</guid><description>Introduction This document describes the in game Arcadian Senate, how it functions, who can join it and what benefits it could have. The senate works by having members vote on motions proposed by other members. Purpose The purpose of the senate is to allow players a degree of self regulation and power over an aspect of the server's functioning. Additionally, it can serve as an influence in upcoming economic features.</description></item><item><title>Treasury</title><link>https://example.org/arcadius/treasury/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.org/arcadius/treasury/</guid><description>Introduction This document describes the imperial treasury system. A relatively simple system for storing the amount of money earned by the imperial government and its relative payout. Purpose To keep track of the economic movement of the server. And to provide payouts to the current emperor and any members of senate or any other government-affiliated organizations that may be added in the future. Concept The concept revolves around storing the amount of money paid in either taxes or rent as funding for the imperial treasury.</description></item></channel></rss>