<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Julie's Document Website on My New Hugo Site</title><link>https://example.org/</link><description>Recent content in Julie's Document Website on My New Hugo Site</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>January 2025 Event - Ravager Escape</title><link>https://example.org/arcadius/events/jan-2025/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.org/arcadius/events/jan-2025/</guid><description>General Concept The general concept of the event is to escape from many Ravagers chasing the player. The player is spawned at the edge of a hill, atop which lies several targets the player must break with snow balls. The player acquires these snow balls by wondering around the hill and dodging Ravagers. Once enough snowballs have been gotten, the player is able to break all targets at the top of the hill and the event ends.</description></item><item><title>Event Setup rules and guides</title><link>https://example.org/arcadius/events/rules/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.org/arcadius/events/rules/</guid><description>Event Rules The following checks must be passed during testing for an event to be considered in 'acceptable' conditions: Dying in the event must remove you from the event instantly and nullify any potential score gain, as well as remove any event-provided items and/or effects. Quitting in the event must do the same as above. It should be impossible to enter the event with potion effects, they must be either: Cleared upon entering Prevented from entering if they possess potion effects Entering the event should function perfectly each time Exiting the event should function perfectly each time Completing the event, different from exiting, should follow the event's context and assign scores only if: The player&amp;#39;s score is higher than their record The event uses the assign-only-if-score-greater rule Alt accounts are not permitted to gain score on the same ground as main accounts, when dealing with an alt, one of the following methods must be used The alt is unable to enter (preferred) The alt is unable to gain score The alt&amp;#39;s score is given to the main The follwing are optional checks which apply on a per-event basis:</description></item><item><title>Arcadian Religion</title><link>https://example.org/arcadius/religion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.org/arcadius/religion/</guid><description>Abstract Religion in the world of Arcadius is polytheistic, worship is split between several gods, and you pray to the god that's relevant to what you're struggling with. For example, if you need luck on a journey over sea, you'd pray to the sea god or goddess. Gods Note: The names used in this list are meant to be faction independent. Faction specific names are listed below. Main Gods Imperator Divius The First Emperor, ascended to godhood after death, the hero-god of humanity.</description></item><item><title>Design Document</title><link>https://example.org/arcadius/dungeons/design/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.org/arcadius/dungeons/design/</guid><description>Abstract The Dungeons, generally, is a rougelike feature of ArcadiusMC, similar to games like Hades, and Pressure (Roblox), with ULTRAKILL serving as inspiration as well. Players will enter the randomly-generated dungeons, fight through rooms of enemies until they find a boss room, fight the boss and then advance on to the next level. The purpose of this document is to outline the methods of implementation for the dungeons. Dungeon Structure The structures that will comprise the Dungeons' levels will be made with the "</description></item><item><title>Dungeons Design Document</title><link>https://example.org/arcadius/dungeons/designdoc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.org/arcadius/dungeons/designdoc/</guid><description>Introduction This document will outline the way players interact with the Dungeons and how systems of the dungeons work. Setup This section describes the way the players enter and prepare for the dungeons. Players can enter the Dungeons at a Dungeon Lobby area, where they are given an option to join an existing dungeon party or create their own. Joining Parties can be joined in one of 2 ways: Be invited, or request to join.</description></item><item><title>Legend of Adis</title><link>https://example.org/marin/legend-adis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.org/marin/legend-adis/</guid><description>Intro The following text is from the book “Fabulam Adis “or “The Story of Adis “it is also known by its longer title “the Story of Adis, the conqueror, emperor and the man who became a god “It was written by Uliksos, an Afinian scholar who sold himself into slavery, he advised Adis and later tutored his son Tulone.
I tell the story of a man named Adis Econius Livius, who later was named Adis Econius Victormagnus Imperator.</description></item><item><title>List of Econian Emperors</title><link>https://example.org/marin/emperors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.org/marin/emperors/</guid><description># Full name Name Begin End Reign Reason Succession Cause of Death Notes 1 Adis Augustus Econius Divinus Victormagnus Imperator Adis -9 26 35 Founded Founded the Empire Old Age 2 Imperator Tulone Econius Divi Filius Adis Tulone 26 31 5 Inherited Son of Adis Killed by the Fyli Fylis The Fyli Fylis would become an untrustworthy guard and would&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;fall to palace intrigue 3 Marcus Econius Divi Filius Marcus 31 33 2 Inherited Son of Tulone Strangeled by his Brother 4 Livius Econius Adis Imperator Livius 33 51 18 Overthrow Killed Marcus and took the throne Old Age 5 Ocatvius Econius Divi Filius Octavius 51 81 30 Inherited Son of Livius Old Age 6 Primus Econius Adis Primus 81 85 4 Inherited Son of Octavius Killed by Rebels 7 Agrippa Econius Adis Divi Filius Agrippa 85 87 2 Inherited Son of Primus Suicide 8 Tiberius Econius Imperator Divi Filius Adis Tiberius 87 103 16 Inherited Brother of Agrippa Old Age 9 Crassius Econius Divi Filius Crassius 103 107 4 Inherited Son of Tiberius Killed by the Fyli Fylis 10 Sextus Econius Divi Filius Sextus 107 131 24 Inherited Son of Crassus Old Age 11 Tullus Econius Divi Filius Tullus 131 136 5 Inherited Grandson of Sextus Killed by the Fyli Fylis Was decleared enemy of the State by the Senate 12 Quintus Econius Divi Filius Imperator Quintus 136 138 2 Inherited Brother of Tullus Killed by Flavius Econius Varus 13 Proclus Econius Divi Filius Proclus 138 141 3 Overthrow Hailed Emperor by the Fyli Fylis Killed by the Fyli Fylis 14 Flavius Econius Divi Filius Varus Flavius 141 164 23 Overthrow Sezied the Throne Old Age 15 Severus Econius Imperator Adis Severus 164 169 5 Inherited Son of Flavius Deposed by Military Tribunate 16 Caius Econius Divi Filius Victormagnus Imperator Caius 169 203 34 Overthrow Hailed Emperor by the Military Tribunate Old Age After death would be&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;given the title of "</description></item><item><title>Merchants</title><link>https://example.org/arcadius/merchants/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.org/arcadius/merchants/</guid><description>Introduction This document describes a system of merchants and tradesmen that richer players can interact with. This sytem allows players to give large quantities of items to merchants, who then "embark" on a voyage to sell the goods overseas. All funds earned from selling are then returned to the player(s) from whom the items came. Purpose The purpose of the merchants is to provide a way for late-game, richer players to spend their money and earn more without using farms and mass-selling.</description></item><item><title>The First Emperor</title><link>https://example.org/arcadius/first-emperor/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.org/arcadius/first-emperor/</guid><description>Abstract The First Emperor is an almost mythical figure that is worshipped as a god. The true identity of him has since been long forgotten, with each faction that vies over the Empire claiming their faction to be descended from the First Emperor. The real story of the emperor is unknown, even his name is contested. It is unknown if he had children or any descendants. Variations This section will summarize the variations of the Emperor's story that each faction considers true, and then will summarize the real story.</description></item><item><title>The Gods</title><link>https://example.org/marin/gods/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.org/marin/gods/</guid><description>List of gods Adis King of the Gods. God of Justice, Hero-God of Humanity, Honor and luck Uwmus God of War, Life and Death Yarus God of Work, Commerce and Trade. Judius God of the Harvest, the Hunt and the Weather. Uhuna Godess of Love, Sex, Mercy and Forgivness Juno Godess of Wisdom, Science and Logic. Info The Gods live atop the Holy Mountain of Hadria (Afin Region) in an expansive palace.</description></item><item><title>The Latins Senate</title><link>https://example.org/arcadius/senate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.org/arcadius/senate/</guid><description>Introduction This document describes the in game Arcadian Senate, how it functions, who can join it and what benefits it could have. The senate works by having members vote on motions proposed by other members. Purpose The purpose of the senate is to allow players a degree of self regulation and power over an aspect of the server's functioning. Additionally, it can serve as an influence in upcoming economic features.</description></item><item><title>Treasury</title><link>https://example.org/arcadius/treasury/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.org/arcadius/treasury/</guid><description>Introduction This document describes the imperial treasury system. A relatively simple system for storing the amount of money earned by the imperial government and its relative payout. Purpose To keep track of the economic movement of the server. And to provide payouts to the current emperor and any members of senate or any other government-affiliated organizations that may be added in the future. Concept The concept revolves around storing the amount of money paid in either taxes or rent as funding for the imperial treasury.</description></item></channel></rss>