<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Dev Journal on My New Hugo Site</title><link>https://example.org/delphi/devjournal/</link><description>Recent content in Dev Journal on My New Hugo Site</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://example.org/delphi/devjournal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>28-01-2025</title><link>https://example.org/delphi/devjournal/28-01-2025/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.org/delphi/devjournal/28-01-2025/</guid><description>Intro It's been weeks, maybe even months since I've touched this project... oh god. I started finally implementing the renderer I created in the delphirender module. Starting with a very simple Flow layout that just places elements after each other. I'll implement the rest of the layout once I know the configuration and projection of entities is correct. Afterword It's 7 hours later. I hate this project... I spent almost all of today thinking about and fixing issues related to the most simple parts of rendering and layout possible.</description></item><item><title>05-02-2025</title><link>https://example.org/delphi/devjournal/05-02-2025/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.org/delphi/devjournal/05-02-2025/</guid><description>Today I'll most likely be fixing yesterday's bugs, getting the Flow layout completely functional with auto margins and stuff. I started by adding support the box-sizing property to Chimera and NLayout. The offset bug I described yesterday. The blue is where the black background is intended to be located. The item element (pickaxe) is also wildly offset from where it is intended to be. Another bug to fix... On top of the previous bug, when a page is spawned, the backgrounds, outlines and anything other than content is blank, resulting in this.</description></item><item><title>06-02-2025</title><link>https://example.org/delphi/devjournal/06-02-2025/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.org/delphi/devjournal/06-02-2025/</guid><description>The Day started with me testing the measurement system only to find out it worked... like as far as I could see, it worked. This was unexpected. There were some visual bugs I found, that I fixed after adjusting the BLOCK_OFFSET_X from yesterday to 0.0717 which was more accurate. And by making regular text render objects also apply the offset. (Before, only the empty text displays used the offset) The results produced by this were actually really good and fixed a visual error I encountered this morning: Before adjusting the constant.</description></item></channel></rss>