<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Marin Universe on My New Hugo Site</title><link>https://example.org/marin/</link><description>Recent content in Marin Universe on My New Hugo Site</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://example.org/marin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Legend of Adis</title><link>https://example.org/marin/legend-adis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.org/marin/legend-adis/</guid><description>Intro The following text is from the book “Fabulam Adis “or “The Story of Adis “it is also known by its longer title “the Story of Adis, the conqueror, emperor and the man who became a god “It was written by Uliksos, an Afinian scholar who sold himself into slavery, he advised Adis and later tutored his son Tulone.
I tell the story of a man named Adis Econius Livius, who later was named Adis Econius Victormagnus Imperator.</description></item><item><title>List of Econian Emperors</title><link>https://example.org/marin/emperors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.org/marin/emperors/</guid><description># Full name Name Begin End Reign Reason Succession Cause of Death Notes 1 Adis Augustus Econius Divinus Victormagnus Imperator Adis -9 26 35 Founded Founded the Empire Old Age 2 Imperator Tulone Econius Divi Filius Adis Tulone 26 31 5 Inherited Son of Adis Killed by the Fyli Fylis The Fyli Fylis would become an untrustworthy guard and would&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;fall to palace intrigue 3 Marcus Econius Divi Filius Marcus 31 33 2 Inherited Son of Tulone Strangeled by his Brother 4 Livius Econius Adis Imperator Livius 33 51 18 Overthrow Killed Marcus and took the throne Old Age 5 Ocatvius Econius Divi Filius Octavius 51 81 30 Inherited Son of Livius Old Age 6 Primus Econius Adis Primus 81 85 4 Inherited Son of Octavius Killed by Rebels 7 Agrippa Econius Adis Divi Filius Agrippa 85 87 2 Inherited Son of Primus Suicide 8 Tiberius Econius Imperator Divi Filius Adis Tiberius 87 103 16 Inherited Brother of Agrippa Old Age 9 Crassius Econius Divi Filius Crassius 103 107 4 Inherited Son of Tiberius Killed by the Fyli Fylis 10 Sextus Econius Divi Filius Sextus 107 131 24 Inherited Son of Crassus Old Age 11 Tullus Econius Divi Filius Tullus 131 136 5 Inherited Grandson of Sextus Killed by the Fyli Fylis Was decleared enemy of the State by the Senate 12 Quintus Econius Divi Filius Imperator Quintus 136 138 2 Inherited Brother of Tullus Killed by Flavius Econius Varus 13 Proclus Econius Divi Filius Proclus 138 141 3 Overthrow Hailed Emperor by the Fyli Fylis Killed by the Fyli Fylis 14 Flavius Econius Divi Filius Varus Flavius 141 164 23 Overthrow Sezied the Throne Old Age 15 Severus Econius Imperator Adis Severus 164 169 5 Inherited Son of Flavius Deposed by Military Tribunate 16 Caius Econius Divi Filius Victormagnus Imperator Caius 169 203 34 Overthrow Hailed Emperor by the Military Tribunate Old Age After death would be&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;given the title of "</description></item><item><title>The Gods</title><link>https://example.org/marin/gods/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.org/marin/gods/</guid><description>List of gods Adis King of the Gods. God of Justice, Hero-God of Humanity, Honor and luck Uwmus God of War, Life and Death Yarus God of Work, Commerce and Trade. Judius God of the Harvest, the Hunt and the Weather. Uhuna Godess of Love, Sex, Mercy and Forgivness Juno Godess of Wisdom, Science and Logic. Info The Gods live atop the Holy Mountain of Hadria (Afin Region) in an expansive palace.</description></item></channel></rss>