<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Arcadius Universe on My New Hugo Site</title><link>https://example.org/arcadius/</link><description>Recent content in Arcadius Universe on My New Hugo Site</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://example.org/arcadius/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Arcadian Religion</title><link>https://example.org/arcadius/religion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.org/arcadius/religion/</guid><description>Abstract Religion in the world of Arcadius is polytheistic, worship is split between several gods, and you pray to the god that's relevant to what you're struggling with. For example, if you need luck on a journey over sea, you'd pray to the sea god or goddess. Gods Note: The names used in this list are meant to be faction independent. Faction specific names are listed below. Main Gods Imperator Divius The First Emperor, ascended to godhood after death, the hero-god of humanity.</description></item><item><title>Merchants</title><link>https://example.org/arcadius/merchants/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.org/arcadius/merchants/</guid><description>Introduction This document describes a system of merchants and tradesmen that richer players can interact with. This sytem allows players to give large quantities of items to merchants, who then "embark" on a voyage to sell the goods overseas. All funds earned from selling are then returned to the player(s) from whom the items came. Purpose The purpose of the merchants is to provide a way for late-game, richer players to spend their money and earn more without using farms and mass-selling.</description></item><item><title>The First Emperor</title><link>https://example.org/arcadius/first-emperor/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.org/arcadius/first-emperor/</guid><description>Abstract The First Emperor is an almost mythical figure that is worshipped as a god. The true identity of him has since been long forgotten, with each faction that vies over the Empire claiming their faction to be descended from the First Emperor. The real story of the emperor is unknown, even his name is contested. It is unknown if he had children or any descendants. Variations This section will summarize the variations of the Emperor's story that each faction considers true, and then will summarize the real story.</description></item><item><title>The Latins Senate</title><link>https://example.org/arcadius/senate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.org/arcadius/senate/</guid><description>Introduction This document describes the in game Arcadian Senate, how it functions, who can join it and what benefits it could have. The senate works by having members vote on motions proposed by other members. Purpose The purpose of the senate is to allow players a degree of self regulation and power over an aspect of the server's functioning. Additionally, it can serve as an influence in upcoming economic features.</description></item><item><title>Treasury</title><link>https://example.org/arcadius/treasury/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.org/arcadius/treasury/</guid><description>Introduction This document describes the imperial treasury system. A relatively simple system for storing the amount of money earned by the imperial government and its relative payout. Purpose To keep track of the economic movement of the server. And to provide payouts to the current emperor and any members of senate or any other government-affiliated organizations that may be added in the future. Concept The concept revolves around storing the amount of money paid in either taxes or rent as funding for the imperial treasury.</description></item></channel></rss>