<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Writings on My New Hugo Site</title><link>https://juliewoolie.com/writings/</link><description>Recent content in Writings on My New Hugo Site</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://juliewoolie.com/writings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Random mini stories</title><link>https://juliewoolie.com/writings/mini/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://juliewoolie.com/writings/mini/</guid><description>Uriel Sobs A choir of divine angels, their wings as white as the very clouds upon which they lay. Their robes torn by iron blades. Screams erupt from them as the final realization sets in: There is no god, they were created by nothing and for no one. For a millennia they shall scream in longing for a god that does not exist, for a god that will not hold or cradle them.</description></item><item><title>Unreality</title><link>https://juliewoolie.com/writings/unreality/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://juliewoolie.com/writings/unreality/</guid><description>Surely reality is not the space which I inhabit, surely reality would be more exciting, more substantive than this dull existence. I live in a single room and while I wish I could claim it was a room with a view of the Seine in Paris, or with a view of the Oder, the Rhine or the Elbe in Germany, it isn't. My view is of another apartment building and these 2 monitors before me on which I type these very letters is my life based on.</description></item><item><title>Comforting Oblivion</title><link>https://juliewoolie.com/writings/oblivion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://juliewoolie.com/writings/oblivion/</guid><description>I know this siren voice within that calls, demands and begs for my end. I know the reasons it gives, the oratories it delivers to me to goad me to the noose. And I can say for certain a great part of the rhetoric comes from a place of deep isolation, a knowledge that better is possible somehow, but that in every way imaginable, it feels beyond my reach. It speaks of the time I lost in isolation and even still continue to lose.</description></item></channel></rss>